[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "True or False? The World Bank defines extreme wealth as a daily income of about one U.S. dollar and ninety cents per day.",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, even though the number of people living in poverty is currently under ten percent, some people _____..",
        "answer": "think that number should be even lower"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, Taiwan has _____.",
        "answer": "fewer people living in poverty than nearby countries"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? The World Health Organization defines extreme poverty as a daily income of about one U.S. dollar and ninety cents per day.",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? In the past, most people lived below the international poverty line.",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, what percentage of the world’s population lived in poverty in 1990?",
        "answer": "about thirty-six percent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, the global economy has experienced _____ as a result of the COVID-19 pandemic",
        "answer": "major difficulties"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, the number of people in Taiwan who live below the poverty line is _____.",
        "answer": "lower than nearby countries"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? In the past, people had an easy time getting enough education and water.",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In paragraph two, the article begins with “Over the past several decades…” The word “decades” most likely means _____.",
        "answer": "about twenty or thirty years"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to a survey mentioned in the article, Taiwan has the largest percentage of _____ in Asia.",
        "answer": "people considered “high income”"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, the global economy has experienced major difficulties as a result of _____.",
        "answer": "the Covid-19 pandemic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paragraph two states “many countries saw their poverty rates drop…” What does this most likely mean?",
        "answer": "The number of people living in poverty went down."
    },
    {
        "question": "The article states that in 2020, the percentage of the world’s population living in poverty was lower than _____ percent.",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, which of the following countries has a lower percentage of its population living in poverty than Taiwan?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, if you would like to donate some money to a charity, it’s a good idea to _____.",
        "answer": "check to see that your donation will help as many people as possible."
    }
]